<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="TrialTwoPC" name="BitStorm Protocol Testing" security="3" allowsDefaultBootModule="false" icon="tablet" type="Empty">
	<adminPass pass="BitHitsTheFan" />
	<ports>21, 22, 25, 80</ports>
	<proxy time="-1" />
	<portsForCrack val="4" />
	<trace time="-1" />
	<file path="bin" name="RandomPassGeneratorInfo.txt">Thank you for choosing the RandomPassGenerator- 
providing security and peace of mind for VirtuNet users across Orion. 
This software is used to provide safe and secure passwords with a variety of configurable settings.

To use the RandomPassGenerator, open the file and select your password criteria. The RandomPassGenerator will then generate a secure password that meets your criteria. All passwords generated are saved in an encrypted file for safekeeping in an accessible, yet secure manner.

Your software activation passcode is the first passcode generated by the RandomPassGenerator, and for ease of access is displayed below.

"AlabasterScimitar"

We thank you once again for choosing the RandomPassGenerator from Voltech Digital Security.

Ensuring and Securing your systems since 1124.
</file>
	<file path="bin" name="RPGSCE_READ_PLS_ZAZ.TXT"> Ohai Zaz I got teh source code for the RPG for j00, lol.
GG EZ NO RE amirite? Dbl Rnbws all teh way across the VirtuNet nao!!1!1!
-Teh 133t TESEO
PS: Passw0rd is in teh info txt file, kthxbai
</file>
	<file path="bin" name="RandomPassGeneratorSCE.exe">ALL UR PASSWORDZ R BELONG 2 US NAO KTHX - TESEO
#BINARY#</file>
	<file path="bin" name="RPGSECUREPASSWORDS.SEF">#BINARY#</file>
	<file path="home" name="Bitstorm Protocol Notes.txt">The Bitstorm Protocol is a highly experimental failsafe encryption software.
Firstly, it corrupts all vital system files, including logs and contents of the /bin directory by randomly swapping ones and zeroes in the basic binary format the files are composed of.
Secondly, the now-corrupted files are then converted to the Secure Encryption Format, A.K.A. SEF, which, so far, is impossible to crack into without very specialized tools or the program that securely encrypted it, and the file is corrupted further.
From there the corrupted, encrypted file is encrypted into a third format chosen at random by the protocol, corrupted one last time, and then the file is completely scrubbed from memory. The first phase is complete in less than thirty seconds, and so far has proven to be irreversable.
Also, a unique function of the Bitstorm Protocol is that it can be used also to target computers linked to the central hub- in other words, the computer the protocol was initated on. This is is intended be used to avoid compromisation of backup servers. However, this program is intended to be used as a LAST RESORT FAILSAFE in the event of imminent compromise of security or anonymity.

-File translated from Akarian by DocuTranslate.net- the best choice for discreet document translation.-

Teseo wuz heer, lol
</file>
</Computer>
